I. M. Pei Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Projects Completed/Inactive, 1959-2013 (Box 136-377)
  - Cleveland, Ohio (Box 153)
    - Erieview I Urban Renewal Plan and Erieview General Neighborhood Renewal Plan (Box 153)
      - Binders, 1960-1967, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 153, Box 154)
      - General, 1960-1965 (Box 154)
    - Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum (Box 154)
      - General (Box 154)
        - 1986-1991, (3 folders) (Box 154)
        - 1992-2010, (6 folders) (Box 155)
      - Opening, 1995 (Box 155)
      - Topical files, 1987-1997 See also Container OV 3, Cleveland (Box 155)
  - Columbus, Ind., Cleo Rogers Memorial Library, 1973-1976, 1985, 1994-1996 See also Container OV 31, Columbus, (1 folder) (Box 155, Box 156)
  - Dallas, Tex. (Box 156)
    - Dallas City Hall (Box 156)
      - General, 1973-1980, 1992-2009, (3 folders) (Box 156)
      - Henry Moore sculpture, 1974-1978 (Box 156)
      - Photographs, 1986 (Box 156)
      - Plaza exhibit, 1984-1985 (Box 156)
    - Fountain Place (originally Allied Bank Tower), 1982-1986 (Box 156)
    - Morton H. Meyerson Symphony Center (Box 156)
      - Arts acquisition committee (Box 156)
        - 1984-1986 (Box 156)
        - 1987-1989 (Box 157)
      - General (Box 157)
        - 1980-1981, (6 folders) (Box 157)
        - 1982, (1 folder); (6 folders) (Box 157, Box 158)
        - 1983, (1 folder) (Box 158, Box 159)
        - 1984-2006 See also Container OV 18, Dallas, (5 folders) (Box 159)
      - Photographs, circa 1983 (Box 159)
      - Topical files, 1981-1989, (2 folders) (Box 160)
  - Dawhah, Qatar (Box 160)
    - Museum of Islamic Art (Box 160)
      - General (Box 160)
        - 1999-2001, (3 folders) (Box 160)
        - 2002, (2 folders); (7 folders); (3 folders) (Box 160, Box 161, Box 162)
        - 2003, (3 folders); (7 folders); (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box 162, Box 163, Box 164, Box 165)
        - 2004-2007, (6 folders) (Box 165)
        - 2008, (1 folder) (Box 165, Box 166)
        - 2009-2014 (Box 166)
      - Shop drawings (Box 166)
        - 2003, Nov., (2 folders) (Box 166)
        - 2003, Dec., (4 folders); (5 folders) (Box 166, Box 167)
        - 2004, Jan., (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box 167, Box 168)
        - 2004, Feb., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 168, Box 169)
        - 2004, Mar., (5 folders) (Box 169, Box 170)
        - 2004, Apr., (1 folder); (7 folders) (Box 170, Box 171)
        - 2004, May, (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box 172, Box 173)
        - 2004, June, (4 folders); (6 folders) (Box 173, Box 174, Box 175)
        - 2004, July, (3 folders); (6 folders) (Box 175, Box 176, Box 177)
        - 2004, Aug., (7 folders) (Box 178, Box 179, Box 180, Box 181)
        - 2004, Sept., (6 folders); (7 folders); (2 folders) (Box 182, Box 183, Box 184, Box 185)
        - 2004, Oct., (5 folders); (7 folders); (1 folder) (Box 185, Box 186, Box 187, Box 188)
        - 2004, Nov., (6 folders); (7 folders); (4 folders) (Box 188, Box 189, Box 190, Box 191)
        - 2004, Dec., (3 folders); (6 folders); (7 folders); (1 folder) (Box 191, Box 192, Box 193, Box 194, Box 195, Box 196, Box 197, Box 198, Box 199)
        - 2005, Jan., (5 folders); (7 folders); (3 folders) (Box 199, Box 200, Box 201, Box 202, Box 203, Box 204, Box 205, Box 206, Box 207, Box 208, Box 209, Box 210)
        - 2005, Feb., (4 folders); (7 folders); (5 folders) (Box 210, Box 211, Box 212)
        - 2005, Mar., (2 folders); (7 folders); (6 folders) (Box 212, Box 213, Box 214)
        - 2005, Apr., (7 folders); (6 folders); (4 folders) (Box 215, Box 216, Box 217, Box 218, Box 219, Box 220, Box 221, Box 222)
        - 2005, May, (3 folders); (7 folders); (6 folders); (4 folders) (Box 222, Box 223, Box 224, Box 225, Box 226, Box 227, Box 228, Box 229, Box 230, Box 231, Box 232, Box 233)
        - 2005, June, (3 folders); (7 folders); (6 folders) (Box 233, Box 234, Box 235, Box 236, Box 237, Box 238)
        - 2005, July, (1 folder); (6 folders); (2 folders) (Box 238, Box 239, Box 240, Box 241)
        - 2005, Aug., (2 folders) (Box 241)
        - 2005, Sept., (2 folders) (Box 241)
        - 2005, Oct., (4 folders) (Box 242)
        - 2005, Nov. (Box 242)
      - Stone shop drawings (Box 242)
        - Nos. 0601-0607, 2005, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 242, Box 243)
        - Nos. 9600-9602, 2005, (5 folders) (Box 243)
        - Nos. 9603-9608, 2005, (2 folders) (Box 243, Box 244)
        - Nos. 9622-9641, 2004-2005, (4 folders) (Box 244)
        - Nos. 9642-9665, 2005, (5 folders) (Box 245)
      - Team files (Box 245)
        - Campbell, Deborah (Box 245)
          - Acoustics, 2003 (Box 245)
          - Batch specifications, 2003, (7 folders); (2 folders) (Box 246, Box 247)
          - Concrete, 2003 (Box 247)
          - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 247)
          - Curtain wall, 2003 (Box 247)
          - Doors and frames, 2003, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 247, Box 248)
          - Finishes, 2003, (2 folders) (Box 248)
          - Floor plans, 2003 (Box 248)
          - General conditions, 2003 (Box 248)
          - Interior specifications, 2002-2003, (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 248, Box 249)
          - Leslie E. Robertson Associates, 2003, (2 folders) (Box 249)
          - Miscellany, 2003, (2 folders) (Box 250)
          - Table of contents, 2003, (2 folders) (Box 250)
          - U.S. Gypsum Corp., 2003 (Box 250)
          - Vertical transports, 2003 (Box 250)
          - Waterproofing, 2003 (Box 250)
        - Chin, Perry (Box 250)
          - Al Kuhaimi Metal Industries, 2004, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 250, Box 251)
          - Architectural detail drawings See Container OV 19, Set of drawings (Box 251)
          - Architectural drawings and exterior enclosure See Container OV 19, Set of drawings (Box 251)
          - Architectural drawings, base building See Container OV 19, Bound set of detail drawings (Box 251)
          - Auditorium design drawings See Container OV 20, Drawings for auditorium (Box 251)
          - Awad Architectural Models, 2002-2006 (Box 251)
          - Bari, Hubert, 2004 (Box 251)
          - Baytur Insaat Taahhüt A.S., 2005-2009, (3 folders) (Box 251)
          - Bulletin logs, 2004-2007, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 251, Box 252)
          - Codes and regulations, 1990-2002, (5 folders); (7 folders); (1 folder) (Box 252, Box 253, Box 254)
          - Concept designs, 2002 See Container OV 32, Hand and computer-generated renderings (Box 254)
          - Concrete mix design, 2003 (Box 254)
          - Construction planning, 1999-2003, (4 folders) (Box 254)
          - Construction Specifications, Inc. 1999-2003, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 254, Box 255)
          - Corived, 2002-2004 (Box 255)
          - Corporate identity designs, 2004 See Container OV 3, Two spiral-bound dossiers (Box 255)
          - COWI A/S, 2001-2002, (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box 255, Box 256)
          - Cracknell Landscape Investments, 2005 (Box 256)
          - Davis Langdon France, 2003-2004 (Box 256)
          - Electrical, plumbing, and ventilation drawing sheets, 2002-2005 See Container 21, Three sets of mechanical, plumbing, and engineering drawings (Box 256)
          - Engineering and Research International, 2002, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 256, Box 257)
          - Entek Engineering LLP, 2003 (Box 257)
          - Esto Photographics, 2002 (Box 257)
          - Fisher Marantz Stone, 2001-2007, (5 folders) (Box 257)
          - Flick, Dale, 2001-2002 (Box 258)
          - Formwork sheet drawings, 2004-2005, (3 folders) (Box 258)
          - Fountain drawing sheets, 2003 See Container OV 22, Set of drawings (Box 258)
          - Fountain People, 2005-2006, (3 folders) (Box 258)
          - Grant Thornton LLP, 2003-2004 (Box 258)
          - Graphic designs, 2004 See Container OV 4, Two spiral-bound, graphic-design dossiers (Box 258)
          - Halcrow Consulting Engineers and Architects, 2004-2005 (Box 258)
          - Hausler, Richard, 2003 (Box 258)
          - HAZ Metal Fixing Systems, 2003-2004, (3 folders); (4 folders) (Box 258, Box 259)
          - Hobbs Architectural Fountains, 2002-2004, (2 folders) (Box 259)
          - Hough, Reginald, 2003-2005 (Box 260)
          - Independent Stone Consulting, 2005 (Box 260)
          - Inspections, 2007, (5 folders) (Box 260)
          - Interior and exterior stone cladding, 2003 See Container OV 20, Bound set of drawings (Box 260)
          - Interior architecture design, 2001-2004 See also Container OV 22, Interior drawings, (1 folder); (7 folders) (Box 260, Box 261, Box 262)
          - Invoices, 2002-2009, (3 folders) (Box 262)
          - Islamic Art Society, 2002-2003 (Box 262)
          - Jacoby, Helmut, 2002 (Box 262)
          - Jaras Baum and Bolles, 2001-2008, (2 folders); (7 folders); (6 folders); (3 folders) (Box 262, Box 263, Box 264, Box 265, Box 266, Box 267)
          - Kitchen design, 2004-2005, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 267, Box 268)
          - Landscape layouts and details, 2006 See Container OV 23, Landscape drawings (Box 268)
          - Leslie E. Robertson Associates, 2002-2008, (6 folders); (7 folders); (2 folders) (Box 268, Box 269, Box 270, Box 271, Box 272)
          - Marine works bid package, 2003, (4 folders) (Box 272)
          - McQuay, air conditioning, 2005 (Box 272)
          - Meeting minutes, 2001-2005 (Box 273)
          - Ministry of Municipal Affairs and Agriculture, 2001-2003 See also Digital Files, mss83787_123_040; mss83787_123_041, (6 folders); (7 folders); (3 folders) (Box 273, Box 274, Box 275)
          - Miscellaneous consultants and contractors, 2001-2004, (2 folders) (Box 275)
          - National Council for Culture, Arts, and Heritage, 2001-2008, (2 folders) (Box 275)
          - Northcroft Middle East, 2001-2004, (2 folders) (Box 275)
          - Oles, Steve, 2001-2003 (Box 276)
          - Oliver Hoare, 2002-2003 (Box 276)
          - Pei, I. M., 2001-2007 (Box 276)
          - Photographs, 2005-2007, (4 folders) (Box 276, Box 277)
          - Preliminary design issue, 2002 See Container OV 20, Bound set of early drawings (Box 277)
          - Pre-qualification documents for aluminum and stainless steel items, 2004 (Box 277)
          - Progress reports, 2004-2007, (2 folders); (6 folders); (3 folders) (Box 277, Box 278, Box 279)
          - Prosurance Brokerage Associates, 2002-2003 (Box 279)
          - Punch lists, 2007, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 279, Box 280)
          - Qatar Museum Authority, 2007-2008 (Box 280)
          - Qatar Petroleum, 2004-2008, (4 folders) (Box 280)
          - Qatari Engineer and Associates, 2001-2005, (2 folders); (5 folders) (Box 280, Box 281)
          - Requests for information, 2003-2005, (2 folders); (6 folders) (Box 281, Box 282, Box 283)
          - Research material, 2001-2003, (3 folders) (Box 283)
          - Rolf Jensen and Associates, 2002, (2 folders) (Box 283)
          - Schmidlin LLC, 2005-2006 (Box 283)
          - Security design, 2004-2005 See also Container OV 4, Set of preliminary security design drawings, (5 folders) (Box 284)
          - Shaw Pittman LLP, 2001, (2 folders) (Box 284)
          - Shen Milsom and Wilke, 2002-2003, (6 folders) (Box 285)
          - Shop drawings, 2003-2007, (1 folder); (7 folders); (6 folders) (Box 285, Box 286, Box 287, Box 288, Box 289)
          - Signage, 2004-2005 See Container OV 5, Three spiral-bound dossiers (Box 289)
          - Site plans, 2000-2004 See Container OV 33, Site maps (Box 289)
          - Specifications, 2003-2005, (2 folders); (7 folders); (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box 289, Box 290, Box 291, Box 292)
          - Structural design book, 2003-2005, (5 folders); (3 folders) (Box 292, Box 293)
          - Structural drawing sheets, 2003-2004 See Container OV 24, Two sets of drawings (Box 293)
          - Stumacher, Jeffery, 2003 (Box 293)
          - Subject files, 2000-2007, (1 folder); (8 folders); (5 folders) (Box 293, Box 294, Box 295, Box 296)
          - Submittals, 2005, (2 folders); (7 folders); (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box 296, Box 297, Box 298, Box 299, Box 300)
          - Tecnomarine International, 2004 (Box 300)
          - Turner International, 2002-2008, (5 folders); (6 folders); (7 folders); (2 folders) (Box 300, Box 301, Box 302, Box 303, Box 304)
          - Watson, Oliver, 2002-2004, (2 folders) (Box 304)
          - Wilmotte and Associates, 2002-2007, (3 folders); (5 folders) (Box 304, Box 305)
          - Xu Acoustique, 2002-2003 (Box 305)
        - Demirtas, Aslihan (Box 305)
          - Fence design, 2007 (Box 305)
          - Peninsula, 2007 (Box 305)
          - Restaurant lighting, 2007 (Box 306)
          - Site model, 2007 (Box 306)
        - Hopkins, Stephen (Box 306)
          - Bronze Craft Corp., 2002 (Box 306)
          - Fountains, 2003 (Box 306)
          - Jaros Baum and Bolles, 2002-2003 (Box 306)
          - Leslie E. Robertson Associates, 2002-2003, (2 folders) (Box 306)
          - Mariotti Carlo and Figli, 2003 (Box 306)
          - Miscellany, 2002-2003, (2 folders) (Box 306)
          - New England Stone Industries, 2003 (Box 306)
          - Parking, 2002 (Box 306)
          - Planning meetings, 2002-2003 (Box 307)
          - Walls, 2002 (Box 307)
          - Waterproofing, 2002 (Box 307)
          - Xu Acoustique, 2002 (Box 307)
        - Okamoto, Hiroshi (Box 307)
          - Background information, 2003-2004, (2 folders) (Box 307)
          - Bill of quantities, 2003, (2 folders) (Box 307)
          - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 308)
          - Invitations, 2008 (Box 308)
          - Mechanical, electrical, and plumbing submittals, 2004-2005, (4 folders) (Box 308)
          - Miscellaneous submittals, 2004 (Box 308)
          - Peninsula phase II, 2004-2005, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box 308, Box 309)
          - Permitting, 2002-2005 See also Digital Files, mss83787_123_039, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 309, Box 310)
          - Preliminary design, 2002-2003 See also Containers OV 14-OV 15, Working drawings, (6 folders) (Box 310)
          - Requests for information, 2004 (Box 311)
          - Shop drawings, 2005, (2 folders) (Box 311)
          - Specifications, 2002-2003 (Box 311)
          - Structure submittals, 2004-2005, (3 folders); (4 folders) (Box 311, Box 312)
          - Transmittals, 2004, (2 folders) (Box 312)
      - Topical Files
        - Awards, 2008-2010 (Box 312)
        - Opening, 2008, (3 folders) (Box 313)
        - Photographs, 2005-2008 (Box 313)
        - Presentation material, 2002 See Containers OV 15-OV 16, Three sets of presentation drawings
        - Program and drawings, 2000-2001, (2 folders) (Box 313)
        - Project overview, 2006-2007 (Box 313)
        - Publicity, 2011-2012 (Box 313)
  - Dayton, Ohio, Gem City Plaza, 1977-1981 (Box 313)
  - Denver, Colo. (Box 313)
    - Courthouse Square, 1960-1961 (Box 313)
    - Mile High Center, 1993-2005 (Box 313)
  - Des Moines, Iowa, Des Moines Art Center addition, 1977, 1997-2004 (Box 313)
  - Fort Worth, Tex., Tandy House, 1984-1985, 1995-2002 (Box 313)
  - Garden City, N.Y., Roosevelt Field Shopping Center, 1994 (Box 313)
  - Hague, Netherlands, Beatrixkwartier, 1991 (Box 313)
  - Hong Kong (Box 314)
    - Bank of China Tower (Box 314)
      - General (Box 314)
        - 1982-1985, (7 folders) (Box 314)
        - 1986-2008, (7 folders) (Box 315)
      - Topical files, 1984 (Box 316)
    - Shanghai Commercial Bank, 1999-2000 (Box 316)
    - Sunning Plaza, 1977-1982 (Box 316)
  - Honolulu, Hawaii (Box 316)
    - East-West Center, University of Hawaii, 1984 (Box 316)
    - Pan Pacific Center, 1960-1965 (Box 316)
  - Houston, Tex. (Box 316)
    - Hilton Houston Post Oak (formerly Warwick Post Oak) Hotel, 1979-1982 (Box 316)
    - Texas Commerce Tower and United Energy Plaza (Box 316)
      - Brochure, circa 1980 (Box 316)
      - General (Box 316)
        - 1977-1980, (3 folders) (Box 316)
        - 1981-1984, 2005 (Box 317)
  - Ithica, N.Y., Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art, Cornell University, 1973-1974, 1992-2011 (Box 317)
  - Jakarta, Indonesia, Danamon Square, 1993, 2000 (Box 317)
  - Kansas City, Mo., United Missouri Bank, 1971-1975 (Box 317)
  - Kuwait City, Kuwait, Al Salaam development plan, 1977-1979 (Box 317)
  - Lincoln, Nebr., National Bank of Commerce, 1972-1976 (Box 317)
  - Long Beach, Calif., Long Beach Museum of Art, 1973-1977, (3 folders) (Box 317)
  - Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 317)
    - Century Plaza, 2003 (Box 317)
    - Continental City, 1982-1983 (Box 317)
    - Library Tower, 1983-1987 (Box 317)
    - Ronald Reagan UCLA Medical Center (Box 318)
      - General, 1996-2008, (4 folders) (Box 318)
      - Topical files See also Digital Files, mss83787_123_018; mss83787_123_019; mss83787_123_ 020; mss83787_123_021; mss83787_123_022; mss83787_123_023 (Box 318)
        - 1998-2001, (2 folders) (Box 318)
        - 2006-2008, (1 folder) (Box 318, Box 319)
  - Luxembourg, Luxembourg, Musée d'Art Moderne Grand-Duc Jean (Box 319)
    - General (Box 319)
      - 1990-1995, (6 folders) (Box 319)
      - 1996-1998 See also Container OV 6, Luxemburg, (6 folders) (Box 320)
      - 1999, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 320, Box 321)
      - 2000-2001, (5 folders) (Box 321)
      - 2002-2005, (7 folders) (Box 322)
      - 2006-2009, (2 folders) (Box 323)
    - Photographs, 2002-2006, (2 folders) (Box 323)
    - Topical files, 1992-2007, (3 folders); (6 folders) (Box 323, Box 324)
  - Macau, Macau Science Center, 2002-2011, (2 folders) (Box 325)
  - Manhassett, N.Y., Greentree, 1977-1978 (Box 325)
  - Manoa, Hawaii, East-West Center, University of Hawaii, 1960-1964, 1999, 2012 (Box 325)
  - Marin County, Calif., Buck Institute for Age Research, 1989-2010, (3 folders) (Box 325)
  - Melbourne, Australia, Collins Place, 1970-1975 (Box 325)
  - Miami, Fla., Bank of America Tower at International Plaza, 1979-1982, 2003-2011 (Box 326)
  - Montevideo, Uruguay, Chancellery for United States Embassy, 1959-1972, 1982, 2011 (Box 326)
  - Montgomery Township, N.J., Johnson & Johnson Baby Products Headquarters Complex, 1976-1977 (Box 326)
  - Montreal, Canada, Place Ville Marie, 1973, 1996-2002 (Box 326)
  - Napa Valley, Calif., Dominus Winery, 1987-1995 (Box 326)
  - New Brunswick, N.J. (Box 326)
    - Downtown Development Plan, 1975-1977 (Box 326)
    - Johnson & Johnson World Headquarters, 1974-1983 (Box 326)
  - New York, N.Y. (Box 326)
    - Centurion, 2007-2010 (Box 326)
    - Columbia University Comprehensive Master Plan (Box 326)
      - Binders, 1968-1971, (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 326, Box 327)
      - Reports, 1970, (1 folder) (Box 327, Box 328)
    - 88 Pine St. (Wall Street Plaza), 1968-1973 See also Container OV 6, 88 Pine Street (Box 328)
    - Four Seasons Hotel (Box 328)
      - General, 1988-2000, (3 folders) (Box 328)
      - Renovation (Box 328)
        - Chin, Perry files (Box 328)
          - ArenaVision, 2003-2004 (Box 328)
          - Burgess Steel, 2001-2002 (Box 328)
          - Cerami and Associates, 2001-2002 (Box 328)
          - Client, 2001-2003, (1 folder) (Box 328, Box 329)
          - Contracts, 2000 (Box 329)
          - Coordinated Metals, 2000-2003, (3 folders) (Box 329)
          - Directory, 2000-2001 (Box 329)
          - Doors, 2003-2004 (Box 329)
          - Enclosure, 2001-2002 (Box 329)
          - Enclosure existing, 1990-1991 (Box 329)
          - Entek Engineering, 2001-2004 (Box 329)
          - Finkelshteyn, Igor, consultant, 2001-2003 (Box 329)
          - Fisher Marantz Stone, 2001 (Box 329)
          - Früh Metallbau, 2002-2003, (2 folders) (Box 330)
          - Glass enclosure, 2000-2002 (Box 330)
          - Glass issue, 2003 (Box 330)
          - Howard I. Shapiro and Associates, 2002, (3 folders) (Box 330)
          - Interior, 2000 (Box 330)
          - Israel Berger and Associates, 2003 (Box 330)
          - Jaros, Baum & Bolles, 2002-2003 (Box 330)
          - Keystone Asset Management, 2001-2004 (Box 330)
          - La Strada General Contracting, 2004 (Box 330)
          - Lighting, 2002 (Box 330)
          - Lobby lounge, 2003 (Box 331)
          - Meeting minutes, 2000-2004, (6 folders); (3 folders) (Box 331, Box 332)
          - Metropolis Group, 2001-2004, (2 folders) (Box 332)
          - Pei, I. M., correspondence, 2001-2004 (Box 332)
          - Peter Marino and Associates, 2000-2003, (2 folders) (Box 333)
          - Petrillo Stone Corp., 2001-2002 (Box 333)
          - Planters and trees, 2002-2005 (Box 333)
          - Robuchan Boutique, 2005 (Box 333)
          - Rosenwasser/Grossman, 2001-2004, (3 folders); (4 folders) (Box 333, Box 334)
          - Schedule, 2000 (Box 334)
          - Seasons Contracting, 2002 (Box 334)
          - Sidewalk, 2003-2005 (Box 334)
          - Sketches, 2002 (Box 334)
          - Specifications, 2001 (Box 334)
          - Stone, 2001-2003, (2 folders) (Box 335)
          - Stone calculations, 2001-2002, (2 folders) (Box 335)
          - Stone enclosure, 2000-2003, (2 folders) (Box 335)
          - Structure, 2000-2001 (Box 336)
          - Testwell Laboratories, 2002 (Box 336)
          - Tishman, 2002-2004, (5 folders) (Box 336)
          - Transmittals, 2001-2004, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 336, Box 337)
          - Vild, Donald J., 2002-2003 (Box 337)
          - W & W Glass Systems, 2001-2003, (2 folders) (Box 337)
          - Window calculations, 2001-2002, (3 folders) (Box 337)
          - Window washing, 2000-2003 (Box 338)
          - Wiss, Janney, Elstner Associates, 2002-2004, (2 folders) (Box 338)
          - Zoning, 2000-2001, (2 folders) (Box 338)
        - Shop drawings, 2000-2005 See also Containers OV 34-OV 35, OV 46-OV 49, Four Seasons Hotel, (2 folders); (6 folders); (5 folders); (3 folders) (Box 338, Box 339, Box 340, Box 341, Box 342, Box 343, Box 344)
    - Guggenheim Pavilion, Mount Sinai Medical Center expansion and modernization (Box 344)
      - 1980-1983, (3 folders) (Box 344)
      - 1984-2009, (2 folders) (Box 345)
    - International Design Center development plan, 1983-1986, (2 folders) (Box 345)
    - Jacob K. Javits Convention Center and Plaza (Box 345)
      - General (Box 345)
        - 1978-1979, (3 folders) (Box 345)
        - 1980-1986, (5 folders) (Box 346)
      - Topical files, 1978-1987, (2 folders) (Box 346)
    - Kips Bay Plaza, 1960-1962, 1992-1998 (Box 347)
    - National Airlines Terminal, John F. Kennedy International Airport, 1987-1994, 2005-2011 (Box 347)
    - Republic of Korea Permanent Mission to the United Nations (Box 347)
      - Contracts, 1994-1995 (Box 347)
      - Correspondence, 1994-2004, (4 folders) (Box 347)
    - Republic National Bank, 1978-1981 (Box 347)
    - 383 Madison Ave., Zeckendorf Penthouse, 1998 (Box 347)
    - University Plaza, New York University, 1999-2011 (Box 348)
  - Oklahoma City, Okla., Central Business District Project 1-A Development Plan and General Neighborhood Development Plan (Box 348)
    - 1964-1966, (5 folders); (1 folders) (Box 348, Box 349)
    - 2010 (Box 349)
  - Paris, France (Box 349)
    - Le Grand Louvre (Box 349)
      - American Friends of the Louvre, 1968-1971 (Box 349)
      - Les Amis du Grand Louvre, 2009 (Box 349)
      - Baccarat crystal pyramid, 1988-1990 (Box 349)
      - Carrousel roadway, 1998-2000 (Box 349)
      - Congratulatory letters, 1988-1990 (Box 349)
      - General See also Container OV 36, Le Grand Louvre (Box 349)
        - 1982-1984, (4 folders) (Box 349)
        - 1985, (3 folders) (Box 350)
        - 1986, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 350, Box 351)
        - 1987, (4 folders) (Box 351)
        - 1988, (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 351, Box 352)
        - 1989, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 352, Box 353)
        - 1990-1997, (5 folders) (Box 353)
        - 1998-2013 See also Digital Files, mss83787_123_013, (4 folders) (Box 354)
      - Name files (Box 354)
        - Biasini, E. J., 1982-1995 (Box 354)
        - Chirac, Jacques, 1984 (Box 354)
        - Lang, Jack, 1982 (Box 354)